Hello everyone.
Hello. Hello.
How's everyone doing? It's been a while.
Please die. myas.
So, we'll be playing War Dogs again.
It's been a while, right?
So, lot of playing War Dogs today. Play
War Dogs. I'll be We'll be doing more
helicopter stuff today
and training and like getting used to it
and stuff. doesn't proud as many stuff.
So yeah,
how's everyone? Uh, hope I'm live all
the platforms. YouTube, Twitch, Kick,
Beam X, not Beam, Rumble, and X. Yeah,
I'm live. Nice.
Uh
last time last stream I was having a lot
of issues due to
due to like the stupid internet
being boo.
Yeah.
As long as I can do today's stream, as
much as I can, I'll keep uh going at it.
Yeah,
as mentioned on my next uh my last
stream, as long as I can get like uh
as long as I can get like uh streaming
PC, my PC from back home, uh that will
be really good
for streams and everything. Yeah.
Hello, Gutsy 2007. Hello, Wakam. I don't
know if you're still here, but hello.
Hello. How you doing?
Hello, Kigus. Hope you're doing well.
Um, give me a minute.
Oh, yeah. We are kind of
kind of going good, I guess.
Twitch. How's Twitch doing? Oh, Twitch
is going well.
That's nice.
Twitch coin is doing okay in there.
Uh what the
okay war dogs let me launch the game. I
actually closed it but yeah I was a like
the potato mode work by uh by by
tinkering around the in game files like
the config file cuz my PC is not able to
stream on low settings man.
Yeah, it is rough
and playing this game.
Yeah, it is really tough.
But it's
I hope
uh one second.
I want to know like adjust the clock a
bit and make it smaller this time for
this scene specifically.
Oh,
thank you for spamming. [laughter]
Hello. Hello. Welcome.
Hello. Hello.
Hope you're doing well.
Hope you're doing well. Hello. Hello.
Good evening.
How you doing?
Okay.
Okay. More jokes. How is it going? Uh,
okay. Slowly loading.
Everything seems to be fine.
con.
I should just close my brows here.
FBI
say I have dual PC set up. and
everything. I only have to keep my
discord and like the game open in my
game uh on my laptop and I'll stream to
my
get everything sorted with uh second PC
which I'll get back from home I guess.
86 mgs 86% memory. H
think this should be fine. Let me just
quit background applications and double
check.
Why do I have Xbox app open? Okay, let's
go.
Let's go.
Give me a second.
Reloading in. It'll be so nice honestly
if um by some means I'm able to like see
the obvious betrayed on my screen
somehow. Anyhow,
why I asked for that is cuz
my internet in this dometry is bad. know
it. I want to know when the betray is
bad so I can like somehow
know. Oh, there is a bit issue going on
and stuff.
So yeah.
So yeah, this is the potato mode.
I was able to con uh uh like make some
changes to the config file. get the
potato mode which is only available to
really bad PCs like low-end hardware.
>> But I wanted to practice the helicopter
stuff.
So we'll do it in the training. Why not?
I have to learn the J hook and the
there's a new trend going on on Twitter
on X. That's the G hook.
Yeah,
I really have to learn this.
That is kind of laggy.
See my pieces.
Wow.
Like a hand.
I'm going to hit
I'm going to What am I What am I doing?
Am
I landing or what am I doing?
What the [\h__\h]
Just that. Just that.
It's the turning which is pain. I I can
understand that.
It's the turning which is kind of hard.
For example, if I want to land this.
Oh god,
I just hit that tree. What? How am I
still alive?
I wanted to do more of the
Oh, yeah. View distance is low, I guess.
Look at the speed I'm going, bro.
exam land. Oh my god. Oh my.
Uh, we don't talk about that. That was
bad.
Okay. How do you do this?
How do you actually do this?
>> Spend money to make money.
>> Oh, yeah. Can't change settings. If I
change settings, it'll mess up the
config file. Ah
dang it.
But yawn pitch is there
a
weaker axis of most side. So that's
destroy the filter
swear.
Oh god, then I swear.
Oh, that was a good landing. Okay,
retry.
I should learn how to fly backwards.
That'll be a good training exercise.
Is it?
Oh my god. Damn.
Ah, I hit the trees. This is bad. I want
to be a pilot.
Got the If I carry my troops with this,
>> I carry my troops like this, it won't go
well.
a
video.
Okay.
And how do you uh change your
why I kill troops over here? I'll do it
like this.
What controlling, right? I feel like
and you fly like this.
Ah, shouldn't do that.
Okay. Upside down.
The uh S is going inward. W is going
upward. Okay, got it. I want to do the
reverse thingy.
Let me see what I can do.
Push him up.
Uh, one second.
I realized my streamer mode was not on.
So if I'm all tabbing, will it still
stay in the air or will it still it does
stay in the air the elevation I put?
Huh?
It's up higher elevation.
It will still stand.
Putting the nose up actually. But the
thing is it drifts. No, it drifts
backward. I don't I don't like that.
I don't want it to drift backward.
You're wondering what am I doing? I'm
just figuring out
I'm just trying to figure out the
helicopter controls, I guess.
And we slowly dis desend
right over here.
Ah.
Uh
that is a crash landing.
Mayday,
Mora.
[laughter]
And that is gone.
That is gone.
Y
early training.
Is that a beat?
Okay,
I just remembered to do my Instagram
story.
Okay, this level will be the last one.
>> Then we're going to go into a match.
Okay.
Uh
exam
my destination is here.
Oh [\h__\h]
I did say that was the last one. So
we'll go.
Don't be tired.
All right, let's play. I want to play in
the community. Can I actually play
Uh,
you need a password for that. Ah, I
don't know.
Hello. Welcome.
He's this low.
Why do I have
max three
automatically select the best?
My ping is increasing. Does that mean my
stream is dying?
Why can't I not?
Uh,
no one's here in these big servers.
Yeah.
Okay, that's this one. Oh, that. Let's
go. This.
How you doing?
Welcome D.
How are you? I'm doing great.
I'm doing great.
I wanted to stream in the morning, but I
was so tired.
had a lot of
um I had a lot of stuff to do.
I couldn't stream in the morning.
I had to go.
>> You just can't keep
>> I had to I had to like go
uh attend my seniors like friends
birthday party thingy. my mistake
>> and stuff.
>> And we I ate like good food.
>> Then we watched a movie together,
hanged out with my seniors,
and then I came back home.
So yeah,
here I am.
I don't know what the hell that guy just
said. Wow.
Uh,
mine is yours.
Okay.
Hey, move. Uh.
I'll actually pilot the helicopter
actually.
Hello, it's Anza. Anza, welcome.
That's mine.
Can I just buy like
Where is secondary ammo?
Yeah.
What's up here?
anyone else? There's one more seat.
Okay.
Okay. Two more seats. Okay.
Uh, let's go.
How come you are able to play this game
on a laptop? Is it not Is it not
demanding? It is demanding, you know,
cuz I'm on a single PC playing and
streaming. It is de very much demanding.
But um I have a 5060 on this laptop. The
only bottleneck is my RAM. It's 16 GB. I
should have bought like the 32GB. I
don't but yeah.
But I'll be get uh trying to import or
career my PC from India. my PC. I had um
back home so I could like
um
so I could like somehow
Oh [\h__\h]
they already build stuff.
Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god.
Oh god. Oh god.
I landed perfectly. Yay.
I landed actually. Oh my god. Oh my god.
No. And now now the main part. I just
have to deliver the supplies.
Oh, I'm getting money.
prophet.
Okay. Slowly, slowly, slowly.
And press
G. Yay. Pilot level two.
Now I go back slowly
up up. So back what on what I was
saying. Move the mouse here. Why? Okay.
Wait. I have to have to learn how to
file it properly. Yeah, need to work on
my landing skills. Not good at it. I
take time to land the helicopter, but
it's okay. Coming back to what I was
saying. Um,
yeah, I feel like currently I don't know
how the stream quality is like, is this
lagging? I'm currently like even with
like changing the in-game in-game config
file engine file to put to put like
everything on low settings.
Um
um low settings. I feel like there's lag
and like the motion is not too fluid.
That's why I feel like I should That's
why I was like feeling yeah I can if I
get my second PC I can like uh like
enlist the load of streaming and then
recording to that PC. I just send the
feed of the current one the game and
like audio and stuff from my game from
the laptop. That'll be better, right? I
used to do it. So I know
the thing like back in India when I had
my two PC setup right I used to stream
like heavy demanding games cuz I had two
pieces set up. The only issue back then
was like oh I can unlock this getting
this.
Uh
the only issue was like
uh l uh like the lag and everything.
Like the only issue was the lag.
Okay. Uh,
why is there no players? Anyone want to
ride back home?
Come, come in.
No lag.
That is fine. But uh the thing is not I
feel like the FPS,
don't I? I just want a smooth motion as
much as possible.
And these guys are pro pilots. Look at
him flying.
Why is there no people? Get on my Get on
my thing.
Okay, someone's coming. Please come come
on my Please get on my No, don't go
down. Yeah. Get on me. Get Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
More players. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yeah. Come on. Come on. Come on. I want
you. No. Come here. Come here. Come
here. Come here. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Thank you. Let's go.
Yay. Okay. I got two two people.
Let's go.
Pilot jock next is here.
Take parachutes if you don't have it.
Wait. Player named K. He doesn't have a
parachute. Get it from my inventory of
the helicopter. I bought like six
parachutes. Get it.
Okay, I have to descend. Start
descending here.
Yeah, I'm trying to descend. Why is
taking so long? I'm not good at good at
this.
Hey,
extract. Thank you. I'm sorry for
dropping you here and not in the base
because I'm bad at Oh, good, good, good.
No, no, no, no. Oh, oh, thank God. Thank
God.
And now I'm here then the base. Press G
a little bit more.
Uh, and press G. Okay.
Oh, level three. Let's go. More. More.
More customers. Let's go. I'm the air
Uber.
[\h__\h]
[laughter]
No. My helicopter.
No.
My hel my helicopter.
Please stop. Thank you. Kind person. He
he gave out seven seven.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you. taking my use.
Ah, that that big tree, bro.
That big tree.
Where is this truck?
Oh my god. It went all the way back. My
my helicopter.
Well,
celebrated too early. Yeah, should have
taken bite and then go went back.
Thank you.
I'll go back to base and get another
helicopter.
Let me heal up.
Ah, three bandages.
It's okay. Okay. Progression.
Okay. Pilot three. So, I can unlock this
mini gun one. Level four. Okay. Good. I
want to get No. Uh, I want to get level
10. This big one. I can get like 11
passengers
and stuff. That is so nice. Large armor
crate. Level 15. Okay.
This one has a mini gun. Optional
logistic crates. Wait, so does the other
one have? Yeah, logistics cray. Yeah.
Yeah, I can put like cr uh like pallets,
big pallets of building supplies, ammo
supplies, or mechanical supplies or uh
what else? Oil supply stuff. Yeah. Yeah,
the pallets is something I need. I can
level up my support and also the flying.
Yeah.
Ah, a minus 5k dollars. Ah.
Oh, I got money from player assist.
Nice.
Hello.
I'm reading your com. I did read your
earlier comment.
Okay. How far is it? Okay, we're
reaching
H blue team is not really winning.
Hello Kadasa.
Good evening. How you doing?
Streaming after so long. Yeah, I wanted
to stream honestly though. But Thursday
and Friday, I had like my second
part-time job. Um, so I came back home
like at 10:00 after getting on a train
back to my home, walked back home after
eating dinner. I was so tired I slept
off. I think I did wake up like at 3:00
a.m. or 4:00 a.m. I wanted to stream but
I couldn't.
Thank you.
door.
>> Ah, can't use pallets. Dang it. Why am I
getting a 500 slot? I can just take a
small crate now.
Okay, let's do fuel.
Um,
four parachuts.
Any players? No players. No one died.
And yeah, there are people dying.
Anyone? No one. Anyone?
Wow.
I'm literally air Uber D. Come on. I
need players. I need my XP.
Kubo gone. He's also doing the same
thing as me. Okay, there's one player.
Come in. Come in.
Come in.
My services are open. Get in. I won't
give you my customer.
Come on.
He's buying his lord. Okay. Another
player. Come on.
Get him. Yeah. Yeah. Come. Come. Come.
Oh, third player. Okay.
Fourth player. Okay. Oh, he left. He
left. Okay. I'll I'll gather all my
customers.
Okay. Come in. Come. Come. Someone
bought the
uh
this thing.
I got one more player.
Got one more.
Yeah. Good. Good. Good. There's no space
left.
Okay, let's go
on to
our journey.
I feel like landing
>> here is safer. They sure they can like
go there and slowly go in rather than I
do really on top of my head I want to
land here but there are so many trees
it's not that safe.
>> [snorts]
>> So I don't know. I hope they do forgive
me.
But yeah.
Oh, the speed is too much.
Ah, the helicopter is lagging.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, yada yada
yada
yada yada yada
yada yada.
[screaming]
Sorry.
Why did he jump like that? Va,
why did you jump like that?
Thank you.
Um, is that an enemy helicopter?
Oh [\h__\h]
Oh my god. Enemy.
Yada. I'm just an Uber.
I'm your Uber.
Don't kill me. What did I do to you?
Okay, we go back to base.
Get more people.
Honestly though, this is nice.
I need to learn how to land faster.
The J hook.
That is hard for me.
Oh. Oh.
Oh my god.
M. Slowly slowly slowly slowly slowly
slowly slowly. Okay. Good. Good. Good.
[laughter]
Wait. Can I just bring it a bit
to the left?
That's too much. Too much. Too much. Too
much.
Okay.
Okay,
two customers. Oh, one is already in my
thingy.
His name is Nope.
Okay, let's go.
Uber.
Come. Let's put you back to
This is one way to make money.
Yeah.
Can't score. Can't score.
Oh, no. No, no, please, please, please,
no, no, no.
My helicopter.
Ah, the stupid trees that I
Yeah. Hold on. I'm approaching your
position.
>> Someone's coming. Someone's coming.
Is it the same person? [laughter]
I do. Let's get there. Let's get there.
It is not He's not coming. What the
hell?
He didn't even look back. What?
None of the people I
know.
Oh, wait. Will he? Will he?
Nino car.
Uh, I want this plane level 10. It has
like 17, no, 11 seats.
Yeah.
Okay. No one's coming, bro.
Maybe this truck will come.
Mon,
come on. Revive me. Get me a I want to
hitchhike back home. Back to base. I
don't want to re I don't want to
respawn.
Yeah, that is fun.
Is this guy asking
the night? Wow.
No one's going.
>> I'll press respawn back.
>> God damn it.
APC
shotgun.
I love this.
>> Let's at least try to keep it quick.
>> Going to have a cord and buggy.
I want a Humvey though. Hum.
It's so cool. Hi.
>> This guy will take my customers.
mechanical supplies.
Um,
cora
How do I delete this?
He better.
Well, that player come. I just need one
guy.
He's not coming.
Guess I had to go solo.
Yeah, I guess I had to go solo.
If I have if I do low elevation,
I can get more speed
as you can see.
Why speed guy?
Oh my god.
Someone's targeting me.
>> The [\h__\h]
Huh?
>> [groaning]
>> OVER HERE. GET ME UP. [screaming]
SOMEBODY GET ME OUT.
>> OKAY, I think I have to do something
else. I have to kill that bastard.
I love I'm casually saying that. Wow.
Oh yeah, I got like new angle for grabs.
What's up?
Oh,
he
foreign.
I'm going heavy mode.
Just just don't die, Jock.
I'll be super dis disappointed if you
die.
Shinja.
Oh, this he
is doing truck
like he's also delivering supplies and
also hitchhiking people. Wow.
Soya kotana.
So the guy on the green team, he should
be somewhere around this mountain area.
We got to kill him.
So
there that's an attack helicopter. I can
feel it.
This guy also has a basic scope.
I told You can put music.
Is that not a thing?
Oh yeah. I the main goal now I want
not only helicopter stuff. I do want to
get like the bow.
It's a loc.
Ah,
truck is moving too much.
The truck is moving too much.
Damn, look at his skills, bro. Look at
his skills.
Go.
He hit that tree and just kept on
reversing like a Chad. Wow.
>> Okay, I might just make money just by
depositing these to the FOB.
Aren't these mine? Why no one deposited
it? What?
Oh, they have a Sam.
We
should be going out for hunting. I'm not
supposed to be here.
Come on people. Let's hunt.
I want to kill some people.
I'm going commando mode.
I see any if I see any helies, I'll just
I'll just try to
scout.
There's a jet.
Oh,
I see an enemy.
enemy.
That's an attack.
That's an attack helicopter. And that
that was a player over there.
The [\h__\h] is he doing there?
What the hell is he doing there?
So the thing is I have a 3x scope.
Oh, wait. It's a 2x.
Oh, yeah. It's a 3x. Yeah, I do have a
3x co.
So,
as long as I'm not caught, I could
The guy is sniping. I can hear him
snipe. I can hear him snipe.
I just need a pinpoint in his location.
It should be expired right now.
Oh, I see him. I see him.
He's sniping from here. This side.
But But should I risk that though? Isn't
a better guy go around him?
What the? Let's go this way.
Check the corners. Check every building.
There's no one here.
Even if there's no shadows right now,
I should be careful.
Oh, that's a tower. That's a tower.
What the?
Like a hand
like a hands in there.
Okay.
I wish I had a sniper
from playing this long range kind of
moment.
Really much beneficial if I had a
sniper.
What's that hel doing?
There's a player inbound nearby
here.
Is he also sniping?
Yeah.
Like he's there. And that thingy maybe
trying to snipe
or something.
Should I get on the bridge?
Not sure.
But I could though.
Could go. Hel.
Wait. Where did that hel go? It came
from here.
Oh man. Wait. That might be their base.
Oh, they're coming from there now.
So, I have to be careful of this area.
I have to be careful. I'm infiltr
infiltrating.
Let's get there.
Come on.
Snipers.
And there
she may.
Damn, I got like a close look at my
target spotted. Refreshed. What is that?
I feel like this player is like spotting
everything.
trying to spar everything,
every single thing that's happening
here. He's farming probably
kind of
A car.
If I had a file gun, I could have short
shot the helicopter.
That's a player.
At least I'm making money indirectly
like this.
>> Oh [\h__\h]
I got caught. I got caught. I got
caught.
>> I got caught. I got I got caught. I got
There.
Can I
Is that like a radio tower?
That's not the fob.
>> [groaning]
>> Is he down? Is he dead?
I hear someone.
I hear someone. Where where is the guy
who was here?
Ah, he respawned
that. There's a heli.
What's Nice.
Enemy
vehicle detected.
H
the other way uh aircraft came from
here.
>> What was that sound?
>> Hostile vehicle taken out.
Is it landing or is what was that stunt
that guy just did?
It is landing. It is landing. It is
landing.
player.
Player.
Is it not a player?
Okay. So, it's over here somewhere.
Where are the blers?
He dropped someone here.
I wonder I could just raid their base.
It does look empty,
so to speak.
Oh, there's two people.
[\h__\h]
Please don't do it to me. Please.
[groaning]
Please.
You [\h__\h]
>> I I got scared. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
got scared. I was I was like enemy.
>> You You can't hit us.
>> Oh, hi. Uh you can you can take uh
weapon. I just want to uh level up uh
recon. I'll just scout, please.
You can take my weapon. I just want to
scout.
Hey, one second. One second. I'll give
my weapon if you want. I just want my
scout. Thank you.
>> You can't go. You can't go.
>> Wait. Don't take care of you.
>> Hey, uh, can I take my heels?
Okay.
No way. No way. No way.
No way. That just happened.
No way that just happened.
I'll take the gun.
Ah, my PC is lagging.
My bus is the Eli game.
I'm not touching.
I'm not even touching.
I'm not even touching
what
brother
My game is fro.
Did the game ban me or something?
The hell going on?
Oh,
what
game?
Okay.
Y logged out
on there.
That was a good game. Oh my god.
on.
Why? Why? What did I do to deserve that?
Why
don't
and
And
when I was not there,
the boys are judging you. What?
I mean, I was I was I know. I know. I
tried to play it safe. I let those
people not kill me, the enemy. I tried
to negotiate. They let me live. But the
the game crashed on me. My PC was
lagging. Everything was lagging. That
was unfortunate. You know, I had a
revenge plan actually.
So, I wish that was requested. What? Did
I get banned for teaming? What?
What?
I kind of join though.
Well, I was wanting to take the AK and
shoot him, you know, but that's like
sabotaging.
The moment I was thinking what to do,
the game lag happened and I got logged
out.
Go away.
Wow.
I am
Wait, why is it kicking me? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Why is it kicking me? What did I
do?
I can't join.
What is going on?
Yeah. Is Is that what
weird
weird?
Get me in.
At least I can be a pilot,
you know. New game.
I did have a profit of 4K
just from
just from like
sculpting.
>> What are you buying? You got to spend
money. You just can't keep away.
>> Yeah, I'll get that pilot.
>> Make it quick. You got to spend money to
make money.
>> Okay, recon is eight. I have to get it
to 10 to get the good sniper rifle.
Okay, quickly go and buy.
Why can't I run? Hello. Excuse me.
After
the
first I'm the first one to get the
helicopter here. So, let's go.
Huh?
Bro, that's mine.
What?
Huh? That's mine. Okay, never mind.
Never mind. The Wait, what?
But maybe that's mine.
That is mine. Okay, I will [\h__\h] go
away. Hell,
will people even come here?
No, they won't. Come on.
Get in.
Maybe I should Maybe I should go back.
I got this one guy coming. Yeah. Come
in. Come in. Yeah. Come in. Yeah. Yeah.
More the customers, the more the money.
What
did he just die? Did he just switch
teams?
Okay. Even if it's one person. Let's go,
man.
Man, this guy has a full party score.
Look at him.
I'm happy with my one person.
I should have taken some supplies at
least.
Hi,
Jo.
Oh, there's a tower here. Okay.
But you can't take that tower sadly.
Oh god, there's so many. Enemy
helicopters.
Okay, I'm going back. Be careful. I'm
out there, my guy.
You got this.
Oh god, there's someone landing on top
of the
If I had If I had unlocked the If I only
had unlocked the attack helicopter, I
would have shot them down by now.
But sadly, I don't have it yet.
Wait, I didn't get money for
Huh.
What the I did not get money
for transporting that guy. Did he die or
something? No. Right.
There's so many helicopter guys. [\h__\h]
Oh, there are so many customers.
So many customers.
So many customers. Come on. Come on. Get
in. Get in. Get in. Get in. Get in. One
customer, bro. Come on.
[\h__\h] you. Oh my god.
Why go for the big one?
Please. Please.
Why are you going for the big one?
Yes. Thank you. Good customer. always
say as good.
Wait, did he leave? What the hell? What
the hell? What the hell?
What the hell?
Oh my god, I'm so pissed. Just cuz I
bought some supplies, you had to just
leave. Leave. Are you kidding me right
now?
Nah.
Go take
Bro, come. Just get in before the other
people
>> don't get what you're saying cuz I don't
know Chinese.
Why the hell is the blue team so dumb?
Anti- red.
Other people, other choppers are coming
back.
I just need one guy.
again. I'm going to
I'm just going
What is he saying?
What does he think?
I have to be careful cuz this is a city
map
so it's more apparent.
Hey. Hey.
>> Oh [\h__\h] Oh [\h__\h] Oh [\h__\h] Oh [\h__\h] Oh
[\h__\h] Oh [\h__\h]
Ah, [\h__\h] sniper.
I didn't know what he was saying.
Oh, do I? [\h__\h] He abandoned me. What is
this situation?
And what map is this?
Oh my god.
There's so many. Ah.
Heck. I should not I shouldn't have done
this. Should have come. should not have
came replica.
What is going on?
I don't even know.
Wow.
You told me to. Okay. Where would I even
land?
I don't have a gear, man.
That's messed up.
That is so messed up.
There's people.
Dang it. Where will I go? What do I do?
I have no idea.
>> [screaming and groaning]
>> He's dead.
There's some people coming with the car.
Ah, people are dropping. [\h__\h]
Yeah, I should just give up.
This is not a battle. I can
>> I want the G is so bad, man.
Uh,
and then I'll get a lot of heals.
I'm going with a 10k load out. God,
just don't die. Okay,
>> money
load out.
Don't you dare die.
Is he not coming or what's up?
Okay, he is coming.
I know that feeling. He abandoned his
vehicle because no one's getting on his
aircraft.
This game was pain. No one got on mine.
Only a few people got on mine.
views have zero. Wow.
Can you believe it?
They have zero points.
Yeah, the APC is there and the jet
whatever.
Should I just exit?
Uh, this is not a bad spot. I just wish
there isn't enemies here.
Not a bad spot, actually.
That's scary cuz there could be
people
that side.
Spot a bandit. Head on a swivel.
Could
be a stupid sniper in there.
Wait, who got the tower again? Us.
Okay. Enemy got it.
And I like
and I like somehow
I want to kill that guy.
Now the question is how can I do that
safe and soundly
Oh [\h__\h] I'm getting sniped. [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I'm getting sniped. [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
I'm still
>> What is this expensive PUBG? Go to
sleep. I mean, tomorrow is Sunday.
[\h__\h] He saw me. He saw me.
ought to be none there.
This is a good way to go.
Hostile vehicle taken out.
>> Okay, I have to not panic.
>> Take it easy.
There are snipers.
[groaning]
Someone died over there.
and snipe me.
[\h__\h] I panicked. I panicked. I
panicked. I panicked. [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I panicked. I panicked. [\h__\h] I
panicked.
I just let everyone know that I'm here.
[\h__\h]
I hear him.
I do hear him. I don't know where he is.
It had to land on me. [\h__\h]
Why am I playing like a sitting duck?
Please go ahead.
Please.
I can't need a reposition myself.
I don't really position myself.
There's no one there, right?
How do I get inside?
That's a good question. How do you get
inside?
If they can if he can open the gate
somehow
I hear him.
There is someone.
[\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you.
[\h__\h] you. Oh my god. I want to
follow
>> [groaning]
>> Ah, I was muted. Oh [\h__\h] I was muted. I
did not know. [\h__\h] Sorry.
I was muted. Oh my god.
Thanks so much. I was saying so many
things.
I didn't know I'd know I was muted.
My internet
be paying
Internet one.
[groaning]
No one's coming to a circle. Going to
circle. What? Ah, he looted my body.
What?
Stop loading me, you jerk.
And I
[crying]
Okay. Rocka.
What is this expensive PUBG?
It's Vox.
It's fun. It's better than PUBG.
>> You've got some good taste.
>> Why did I just raise 30K again?
Now you're building the fob. Are you
kidding?
There is a lot of team in this area.
Tower three.
Ah, I just went to tower one. No, I
could have went to tower three.
Not there.
I just pray my picture comes back to
normal.
Holy [\h__\h]
Oh, the stream is loud.
Oh my god. Spawn vehicle is destroyed.
Bro,
what is this guy doing?
Don't risk
us to safety
and do a dial
and I should need to stop buying the two
3x scope.
Why am I buying a me a long range scope
like 3x scope and stuff with an AR
not do that much like the scope is too
much I feel like
I know I can do the Beijing zeroing
Maya.
Hi, Handa.
Holy Lord Mie.
Mother in Christ.
Let me get out. Let me get in.
Who built this stupid base?
Is this how you even build it?
Okay, now I'm just complaining too much.
Okay, I hit I did hit him.
I did hit him.
I'm going to go finish him.
I can always count on Joent to be
displaced with something. Wow. Am I that
predictable?
Ah, the game is lagging again
and the bit rate is going down again.
Bri, I hate this.
Yeah.
Oh, here's your
move out the Okay, thank you.
A shotgun. Really?
I see people.
How are you? I'm doing great.
I went to my friend's
one of my senpai senpai senior
birthday party. He made like good food.
So many chicken curry stuff.
Different kinds of
like grilled chicken curry. This and
that. This and that. It was really nice.
I I ate from there, watched the movie,
and I came back.
Bro, blue team has zero points.
Nani saw that.
Where is the fighting happening?
>> Hold on. I'm inbound.
>> Where is he?
How are they able to see? I don't get
it.
I can't see it there, but
What is with this internet?
Look at my ping.
98.
God knows how.
I sound so displeased.
Always something.
There's always something.
Damn, look at him go. He just timed it
correctly to land the pallet inside the
walls. That's a pro pilot.
That over there is a pro pilot.
He knows what to use.
>> Target down. Proceed with caution.
FEEL
like the tower is going to be captured.
Hearing
some gunfight. I'll go to a hot zone and
try to get some kills.
I wish to swap out the mag.
Oh, there's enemies.
Two, three, four.
>> I see him. I see him.
>> [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
WHO PUT IT ON with single ammo?
What the hell?
Oh, he has a bow, man.
I want to take his load out. I want to
take his bow.
I want to take his bow.
Wait, someone took my [\h__\h] I have it.
Can I not put attachments?
Okay, I got the bow. I got the bow. My
favorite weapon
in all of
all of in all games I love playing.
If I have a go, I'm confident.
Where is he?
It's literally looking at me like
Why is he not dead?
He is dead.
How much bow it ammo I have?
Come on.
Kobe Bryant,
I revive you.
How many bows have
I have? 34 arrows
and that is something.
Can you kill people with this? I think
with two arrows, right?
Two or four arrows, I think.
Oh,
cover your back. You cover the front.
Oh, my bit rate is stable now. Yay.
I had.
This is hard.
There's an enemy at base.
Ah, there's a movie.
I should be better off these guys,
right?
Even if those guys
Oh my god, that scared me.
Oh my god.
This is scary.
Enemy
vehicle neutralized.
Yeah, he's alone. I guess can just
snipe him, right?
Roco,
don't tell all the way up
cuz that's just pain.
Hostile attack nearby. Proceed with
caution.
Why is there
[\h__\h] I think I got I think I got seen.
He's not here.
[\h__\h] Where did he come from,
bro?
He's looting everything.
[panting] He's looting everything. This
brat.
This brat.
There's a brat.
Oh my god.
There's [\h__\h]
[groaning]
Oh [\h__\h]
Oh, these guys are fighting here.
I'm just reset.
Let's see what I can do for you.
One good thing is that I'm leveling up
every recon.
an expensive load,
right? Just go here.
Go here.
I need backup.
[\h__\h] you.
Fair brother.
Okay, everyone. I think my internet is
bad. It's going downhill.
So, we will wrap it up over here. Okay.
Yeah.
My queen is bad.
Yeah, it is unstable.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah. All right.
This won't work
every week when network is on idle.
Okay.
Uh we'll wrap it up over here. All the
people who came by today are Calisan
Swordfish
uh bread that is
uh and
another thing and chamro
and cast. Thank you for coming by.
Uh we'll be wrapping it up over here.
Okay.
Um
I just pray
uh it's
up to this
too much telem.
Thank you for coming by.
Hey, what's up?